so now that we have seen how to compute
manufacturing costs let's do a
manufacturing cost quiz let's say that
we can build a one millimeter square
processor for watches which we will call
watch processor or WP let's also say
that we can build a hundred millimeter
square processor for laptops or we will
call it laptop processor or LP which of
the following is true about their cost
the cost of a laptop processor is a
hundred times the cost of the watch
processor the cost of a laptop processor
is more than a hundred times the cost of
a watch processor or the cost of a
laptop processor is less than a hundred
times the cost of a watch processor